

PROFILE SUMMARY:

Tenacious creative with a passion for learning and using technology to solve problems and impact the life of the end-user in a positive way. Experience working with new and existing websites, landing pages and templates, providing guidance and troubleshooting support to clients.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE:

Web Technologies & Frameworks: HTML,

CSS, AWS, Django, MongoDB **Scripts/UI**: JavaScript, Bootstrap

Web Debug Tools: Chrome DevTools

Versioning and other tools: Git

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Phone: (310) 954.7221

Email: marshaeking@gmail.com Github: github.com/tk1ng

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/taryn-king

EXPERIENCE:

SOFTWARE SUPPORT ENGINEER

Real Geeks | 2019 - Present

- · Provided technical and CRM support for real estate SaaS clients
- Assisted with IDX website builds
- · Managed DNS records using AWS
- Created technical documents and ensured platform guides were upto-date
- Prioritized support requests and used problem-solving and analytical skills to resolve technical issues
- · Worked closely with team to ensure product functioned as designed

WEB DESIGNER

Freelance | 2018-2019

 Facilitated website build and provided technical guidance for online fashion retailer

INSURANCE AGENT

Farmers Insurance | 2017-2019

- Effectively cultivated business relations with clientele through verbal and written communication
- Managed accounts and advised clients on insurance policies
- · Developed coverage solutions based on client need

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES:

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN CERTIFICATE

freeCodeCamp

UNIVERSITY OF SOUTH FLORIDA

2007-2010